当你学会了如何解析 JSON 数据的时候  就可以很简单地
Once you've learned how to parse JSON data, it's pretty straightforward to
解析出我们需要的其它字段
be able to parse the rest of the fields that we need.
因为这不是一个关于 Java 或 JSON 的课程
Since this isn't a course on Java or
我们将给你列出解析代码的要点
JSON, we're going to provide you with the parsing code in the gist below.
这就是主要的代码了
And this is what the gist looks like.
这里有三个辅助方法
There are three helper methods.
第一个用来得到格式化日期
The first is for formatting dates.
第二个用来处理温度的舍入
The second is for rounding temperatures.
第三个将天气预报的 JSON 字符串存入预报的队列中
The third is returning a forecast JSON string into an array of forecasts.
这个方法还将日期与每个预报记录对应起来
This method also handles associating a date with each forecast entry.
我们从当前日期开始  每增加一天就加一
We start with a current date, and we increment one for each successive day.
注意 我们使用了儒略历日期
Notice that we also use Julian dates, which is the number of
这是自从儒略时代（凯撒统治罗马的时期）开始至今的总天数
days that have passed since the beginning of the Julian period.
关于儒略历在讲义中有更多的信息  但是
More information is in the instructor notes below, but
这就是我们的应用能始终如一地处理日期的原因
it's how we'll consistently deal with dates in our app.
这样一来  在比较日期时  我们不必担心
That way, when comparing dates, we don't have to worry about taking into
时区或是夏令时
account time zones or daylight savings time.
使用这些辅助函数来更新获取天气预报的任务
Update the fetch weather tasks to use these helper functions and
doInBackground方法应该返回一个天气预报的字符串数组
the doInBackground method should return a string array of forecasts.
你可以把输出记录下来 从而检查数组的正确性
You can log the output to check that the array is correct.
某天的天气预报格式是这样的
The format of one day's forecast should look like this.